aboutlawsuits.com 2018-02-12

# Privacy Policy - AboutLawsuits.com

AboutLawsuits.com and the sponsoring law firm, Saiontz & Kirk, P.A., work diligently to ensure that all appropriate administrative and technical measures have been taken to prevent unauthorized or unlawful use of your personally identifiable information, and to prevent any accidental loss or destruction of such information.

Neither AboutLawsuits.com nor Saiontz & Kirk, P.A. will sell or willfully disclose personally identifiable information about you to unaffiliated third parties, other than as outlined in this privacy policy.

While AboutLawsuits.com is committed to protecting your personal information, no data transmission through this web site or the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

Any information sent by email or through this Website is not secure and is done so on a non-confidential basis. Information sent over the Internet is done at your own risk. To provide information on a confidential basis, communicate with Saiontz & Kirk, P.A., which sponsors the AboutLawsuits.com website, in person or via telephone by calling (800) 522-0102.

### Collection of Information

Personal information may be collected through this Website in three ways:

a) **Information Supplied by Users:** AboutLawsuits.com and Saiontz & Kirk, P.A. may ask you to provide certain information about yourself, including your name, contact information, gender, age, legal interests and certain other information that may be used to identify you.

b) **Information from Web Server Logs:** Certain information about visitors is collected from our web server logs, such as your IP address, the URLs of the Websites and pages you visit (before, during and after your visit to this Website), the times and dates of such visits, information about the computer hardware and software you use and other information that may be available.

c) **Information from Cookies:** In order to offer and provide you with personalized services, the Firm may use “cookies” to store and help track your information. You may adjust your browser settings or use other means to prevent cookies from being placed on your computer, but doing so may result in reduced functionality and less personalized browsing experience.

### Use of Information

Neither AboutLawsuits.com nor Saiontz & Kirk, P.A. will ever willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about you to any unaffiliated third party without first receiving your permission.

From time to time, AboutLawsuits.com or the sponsoring law firm, Saiontz & Kirk, P.A., may disclose information about you to carefully selected service providers that may be engaged to host this Website or provide other services. AboutLawsuits.com and Saiontz & Kirk, P.A. will require all such service providers to use the information solely to provide the specified services, and otherwise to conform to the requirements of this Privacy Policy.

Information collected may be used to keep you informed about events, and selected products and services that may be of interest to you.

If required to do so by law or if there is a good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process, AboutLawsuits.com or Saiontz & Kirk, P.A. may disclose your personal information to appropriate governmental or regulatory authorities or other entities.

### Sending Information Does Not Form an Attorney-Client Relationship

The transmission of information by email or through this Website does not create an attorney-client relationship between you and and the sponsoring law firm, Saiontz & Kirk, P.A., nor is it intended to do so. The transmission of the Website, in part or in whole, and/or any communication with us via email or through this Website does not constitute or create an attorney-client relationship between Saiontz & Kirk, P.A. and any recipients.

AboutLawsuits.com and Saiontz & Kirk, P.A. do not invite an confidential communication through this website or by email. The information you send is not encrypted and may possibly be seen by others. If you send information by email or through this Website, you accept the risk of a possible lack of confidentiality. To keep your inquiry confidential, please contact Saiontz & Kirk, P.A. in person or by calling (800) 522-0102.

Specific legal questions will not be addressed via email or through this Website.

Content Submitted or Made Available for Inclusion on the Site

With respect to content submitted or made available for inclusion on publicly accessible areas of this Website, this information will be made public on the Internet. Such publicly accessible areas may include comment areas associated with content, articles, blog posts, frequently asked questions or other areas of this Website.
